let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following language is the predecessor to C Programming Language?",
        option: [
            "A",
            "B",
            "BCPL",
            "C++",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "C programming language was developed by",
        option: [
            "Dennis Ritchie",
            "Ken Thompson",
            "Bill Gates",
            "Peter Norton",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "C was developed in the year _",
        option: [
            "1970",
            "1972",
            "1980",
            "1986",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "C language is available for which of the following Operating Systems?",
        option: [
            "DOS",
            "Windows",
            "Unix",
            "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "C is a _ language",
        option: [
            "High Level",
            "Middle Level",
            "Low Level",
            "Machine Level",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: " Which of the following are tokens in C?",
        option: ["Constants", "Variable", "Keywords", "All of the above"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Character constants should be enclosed between _",
        option: [
            "Single quotes",
            "Double quotes",
            "Both A & B",
            "None of these",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "The number of relational operators in the C language is",
        option: ["Four", "Six", "Three", "One"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Array subscripts in C always start at",
        option: ["-1", "1", "0", "Value provided by the user"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "C supports the __ statement to branch unconditionally from one point to another in the program.",
        option: ["continue", "goto", "break", "for"],
        answer: 2,
    },
];
